

bonniesbrightideas@gmail.com
714.392.5346
https://bonniesbrightideas.github.io/
https://www.linkedin.com/in/baongocward

SUMMARY

User-centered Designer with a thoughtful and creative approach to problem solving by combining usability viewpoints to design web and mobile applications with impact. Thrives on creating compelling designs to enhance user experiences to grow brand loyalty, create user delight, and make memorable experiences.

EXPERIENCE

ELI HOME UX/UI Designer | Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

Contracted project to redesign clients' website, worked with stakeholders to conduct needfinding due to Covid, applied qualitative and quantitative user research to explore user needs, card sorted, lead the design vision, sketched, wireframed, tested, and prototyped.

PROJECTS

Virtual Education Website Redesigned | Oct 2020

Redesigned West Hollywood Elementary School's website to enhance virtual learning with UX Research, UI Design, & Frontend Development.

Government Website Redesigned | July 2020

Redesigned the U.S. Department of Homeland Security's Website with UX Research & UI Design to streamline user flows and simplify navigation to improve public perception.

Recycling Mobile App | June 2020

Creation of a social recycling mobile app with UX Research & UI Design to excite and promote conservation and environmental awareness.

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

UTAH TRANSIT AUTHORITY Property Administrator II | Apr 2015 – Oct 2019

Assisted in developing and following UTA's program to preserve and protect real estate assets covering 2,400 acres and servicing 1,400 sq. miles.

- Coordinated real estate and development issues with local governments including municipalities, state agencies, and counties.
- Managed leasing, licensing, maintenance, and securing of UTA property.

CORESTRATEGY CORPORATION Executive Assistant/Marketing Associate | Jun 2014 – May 2015

Supported the CEO by maintaining website and marketing plans, planning client events, and completing typical office tasks, as well as, any other duties as requested.

- Supported preparation of marketing initiatives from the initial stage to final production and delivery.
- Assisted in the development and maintenance of the marketing database, to include client and prospective information.

EDUCATION

UX/UI CERTIFICATE University of California, Irvine | October 2020 **B.S., BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION** University of California, Riverside | June 2008

SKILLS

TOOLS XD, Figma, Sketch, InVision, Photoshop, Lightroom, Illustrator, Visual Studio Code

RESEARCH Data Analysis, User Persona, Usability Test, Storyboard, Guerilla Test, A/B Test, Interview, Survey, Comparative Analysis, User Insight, Empathy Map

PROTOTYPING Site Map, Card Sorting, User flow, Wireframe, HTML, CSS, Java Script, Bootstrap, & Github